A Guide to the Papers of the Prince Edward County Free School 1963-1967
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
Special Collections and Archives, Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
1963-1967
Special Collections and Archives, Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
ca. 50,000 Pieces
Between the years 1959 and 1963, there were no public schools in Prince Edward County, Virginia. After five long years the County and State allowed Prince Edwards schools to reopen. Because the black children of the county had no school during this period of time (the white students attended an all white academy) it was thought best to organize a free school which would pave the way for hundreds of young children to return to school after a five year absence. The Prince Edward County, Virginia (free school) papers are the records of that effort. The papers contain correspondence, reports, photographs and other items, which document this sad period in Virginia History.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
A gift from the Prince Edward County Free School Board of Trustees
Biographical/Historical Information
The small south side county of Prince Edward had by 1963 become both a natural and international embarrassment. The county was one of five locales, which came to be called Brown v. The Board of Education Topeca, Kansas.The State of Virginia responded to the Supreme Court decision with what came to be called massive resistance.
In 1959 the Supreme Court of Virginia struck down Virginia's massive resistance laws. Public school systems throughout Virginia began to implement various programs to comply with the 1954 decision, the county of Prince Edward opted to close all public schools to prevent integration.
From 1959 until 1964, there were no public schools operating in Prince Edward County. In 1963 the Kennedy administration (mainly Robert Kennedy) brought the power of the Federal Government into the debacle in Prince Edward County.
The Federal Government and the United States Justice Department came to an agreement with the State of Virginia to reopen the Prince Edward County Public Schools as soon as possible. It became apparent very quickly that the previous four years had taken a heavy toll on both school facilities and students.
Because of the absence of public education, it was thought that a transitional school was neccessary until the public schools would reopen. The Free School was a result of cooperation between the Prince Edward County Public School and the Free School Association, which was formed in the summer of 1963. For a period of one year, the Prince Edward County Free School Board of Trustees took the place of the Prince Edward County School Board.
According to "The Story of the Prince Edward County Free School" "A former Governor of Virginia, Colgate W. Darden, Jr., served as chairman of a six-man, biracial board of trustees composed of leading educators of the state who were to govern the new system's program. The other trustees who agreed to serve at the request of Governeor Harrison were Dr. Fred C. Cole, President of Washington and Lee University; Dr. Robert P. Daniel, President of Virginia State College; Dr. Thomas H. Henderson, President of Virginia Union University; Dr. Earl H, McClenney, President of St. Pauls College, and Dr. F.D.G. Ribble, retired dean of the University of Virginia Law School. A New York Educator, Dr. Neil V. Sullivan, who had attained success with the most modern educational methods including non-graded instruction, was employed as school superintendent." The Board of Trustees were able to raise more than one million dollars to support the Free School Association during it's existance. The Free School was in existance for only one year 1964-1965.
Scope and Content
The Prince Edward County (VA) Free School Association Papers document one aspect of Virginia's Massive Resistance to public school integration. Minutes, correspondence, reports, financial records, teachers and student records, vividly show the damage done to the African American Community during the time frame 1959-1963.
Series Description
Series I. Board of Trustees Minutes, Correspondence and Governance 1963-1967 Boxes # 1-3
Sub-Series A. Minutes Box # 1 The mission of the Free School Association was to begin the restoration of a public school educational system in Prince Edward County Virginia. The Minutes document their efforts to acquire funds, equipment, and the approval of a curriculum.
Sub-Series B. Correspondence Boxes # 1-3 Correspondence of the Board of Trustees with State, Federal Officials, members of the board, and various individuals not directly connected to the Free School Association.
Series II. The Office of the Treasurer/Secretary Boxes # 4-7 The Treasurer was a member of the board of trustees. And in that position was responsible for: The Budget, Expenditures, Payroll Development, and all donated and loaned equipment.
Series III. Office of the Business Manager Boxes # 8-17B The Business Manager was responsible for the day-to-day operation of the free school. Included in this series are several boxes of cancelled checks.
Series IV. Office of the Superintendent Boxes # 18-29 Dr. Neil Sullivan was selected as the superintendent of the Free School Association because of his experience with a non-graded school system.
Sub-Series A. Memo's and Correspondence Boxes# 18-19 -Administrative memos and correspondence. Arranged Chronologically
Sub-Series B. Correspondence Boxes # 20-22 General Correspondence, Arranged Chronologically.
Sub-Series C. Correspondence by folder heading Boxes # 23-24 Correspondence maintained by folder heading, arranged alphabetically and then chronologically within the folder.
Sub-Series D. Personal Files Boxes # 25-27 Correspondence, Resumes of prospective employees of the Free School Association
Sub-Series E. Exit Interviews Box # 28 Views of personnel regarding their experience working in the free school, included are some of their recommendations for improvement as observed by them.
Sub-Series F. Student Evaluation Box # 29 Student views of their experience in the Free School. Comments concern instruction, facilities, and their thoughts on the future.
Series V. Administrative Offices of the Free School system Boxes # 30-33
Sub-Series A. The Principals Office Boxes # 30-31 The organization of the Free School System was divided into four administrative groups. The largest numbers of students were assigned to the high school. Office Correspondence maintained by the Principal, is arranged by alphabet and then chronologically within the folder. Correspondence addresses a wide range of topics, employment, administrative problems, and the problems of running a high school on a day-to-day basis.
Sub-Series B. Department Correspondence Box # 32 Correspondence and reports from the other administrative units in the Prince Edward County Free School System.
Sub-Series C. Department Reports Box # 33 Most of the units were required to submit a final report for thier units at the end of the school year. This subseries documents the activities of those departments for the school year 1965 to 1965.
Series VI. Literary Box # 33A
Sub-Series A. Reports Box # 33A These reports were generated to inform those involved with the status of the free school. Amongst the reports is a final report issued by the superintendent. In addition there are also a number of progress reports from both the office of the superintendent and some of the other programs being provided at The Prince Edward County Free School.
Sub-Series B. Speeches Box # 33A Neil Sullivan and others were called upon to speak before a number of associations and groups concerning the progress of the free school.
Sub-Series C. Writings Box # 33A Policy Manuals for the Prince Edward County Free School, and several school divisions outside of Virginia.
Series VII. Office of Pupil Personnel Boxes # 34-48 Four years without a public education system devastated the African American school aged population. In order to asset the damage and effect some change the office of Pupil Personnel Services was established. The director of Pupil Personnel Services coordinated the following departments: Guidance, Health, Psychological and social work services.
Sub-Series A. Correspondence Boxes # 34-35 Correspondence with heads of the units reporting to the director of student personnel.
Sub-Series B. Lunch, Daily Reports Boxes # 36-41A Applications for free lunch, menu's for each day
Sub-Series C. Absentees Box # 42 These were required statistics maintained for the state. list of each student's attendance.
Sub-Series D. Attendance Boxes # 43-45 list of each student's attendance. These were required statistics maintained for the state.
Sub-Series E. School Monthly Reports Box # 46 Required by the state of Virginia. Average daily attendance and absentees.
Sub-Series F. Transportation, Students Box # 47 It was estimated that over 1,000 students would need transportation to and from school each day. Included in this sub-series are: bus drivers reports, maintenance records.
Sub-Series G. Special Education Box # 47 Primarily test scores used to place students in Special Education Courses. Arranged by grade and alphabetically.
Sub-Series H. Clothing Box # 48 Applicants from families for clothing assistance, arranged in alphabetical order.Restricted.
Series VIII. Teachers Records Boxes # 49-53
Sub-Series A. Grade Sheets Box # 49
Sub-Series B. Grade Books Boxes # 50-52
Sub-Series C. Text Books Box # 53
Sub-Series D. Summer Recreational Schedules Box # 53
Series VIV. Student Records Boxes # 54-63 Restricted
Sub-Series A. Pupil Registration Cards Boxes # 54-59
Sub-series B. Standardized test Boxes # 60-62
Sub-Series C. Transcripts Boxes 63-106
Series X. Photographs Box # 107
Sub-Series A. Admin Photographs of instructors and administratorsistrative Staff Box # 107
Sub-Series B. Robert Kennedy's visit to Prince Edward County Box # 107 Photographs of the program held in Prince Edward County attended by the Attorney General.
Series XI. Printed Boxes # 107-109
Sub-Series A. Yearbooks Box # 107 The Eagle
Sub-Series B. Newsletters Box # 107 The Moton Eagle The Branch # 2 Informer vol 1-4
Sub-Series C. The Story of Prince Edward Free School Box # 107 A publication commissioned by the Free School in 1964
Sub-Series D. Programs Box # 108 Plays, programs, and other events sponsored by the Free School Association, local P.T.A and The library club.
Sub-Series E. Prince Edward County Pamphlet Box # 108 Pamphlet printed by the Washington Post No Date
Sub-Series F. News clippings Box # 108 Clippings from various newspapers and magazines concerning Prince Edward County.
Sub-Series G. Office Supplies Box # 109 Envelopes, Stationary used by the Prince Edward County Free School
Contents List
- Board of Trustees Minutes, Correspondence and Governance 1963-1967
  - Minutes
    The mission of the Free School Association was to begin the restoration of a public school educational system in Prince Edward County Virginia. The Minutes document their efforts to acquire funds, equipment, and the approval of a curriculum.
    - Minutes Aug 17, 1963 (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Minutes Aug 24, 1963 (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Minutes Aug 27, 1963 (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Minutes Sept. 7, 1963 (Box-folder 1:4)
    - Minutes Sept. 14, 1963 (Box-folder 1:5)
    - Minutes Oct. 19, 1963 (Box-folder 1:6)
    - Minutes Dec. 7, 1963 (Box-folder 1:7)
    - Proposed By-Laws August 1963 (Box-folder 1:8)
    - Proposal for Support Aug-Nov 1963 (Box-folder 1:9)
  - Correspondence
    Correspondence of the Board of Trustees with State, Federal Officials, members of the board, and various individuals not directly connected to the Free School Association.
    - Free School Correspondence March - July 1963 (Box-folder 1:10)
    - Free School Correspondence Aug 1, 1963 (Box-folder 1:11)
    - Free School Correspondence Sept. 1-16, 1963 (Box-folder 1:12)
    - Free School Correspondence Sept. 17-20, 1963 (Box-folder 1:13)
    - Free School Correspondence Sept. 23-26, 1963 (Box-folder 1:14)
    - Free School Correspondence Sept. 26-30, 1963 (Box-folder 1:15)
    - Free School Correspondence Oct. 1, 1963 (Box-folder 1:16)
    - Free School Correspondence Oct. 11, 1963 (Box-folder 1:17)
    - Free School Correspondence Oct. 21-31, 1963 (Box-folder 1:18)
    - Free School Correspondence Nov 1-10, 1963 (Box-folder 2:1)
    - Free School Correspondence Nov 11-20, 1963 (Box-folder 2:2)
    - Free School Correspondence Nov 21-30, 1963 (Box-folder 2:3)
    - Free School Correspondence Dec 1-10, 1963 (Box-folder 2:4)
    - Free School Correspondence Dec 11-31, 1963 (Box-folder 2:5)
    - Free School Correspondence Jan 1-16, 1964 (Box-folder 2:6)
    - Free School Correspondence Jan 16-31, 1964 (Box-folder 2:7)
    - Free School Correspondence Feb 1964 (Box-folder 2:8)
    - Free School Correspondence Feb 1964 (Box-folder 2:9)
    - Free School Correspondence March 2-10, 1964 (Box-folder 2:10)
    - Free School Correspondence March 16-26, 1964 (Box-folder 2:11)
    - Free School Correspondence April 1964 (Box-folder 2:12)
    - Free School Correspondence May 1964 (Box-folder 2:13)
    - Free School Correspondence June 1964 (Box-folder 2:14)
    - Free School Correspondence July 1964 (Box-folder 2:15)
    - Free School Correspondence Aug 1964 (Box-folder 3:1)
    - Free School Correspondence Sept 1-15 1964 (Box-folder 3:2)
    - Free School Correspondence Sept 16-30 1964 (Box-folder 3:3)
    - Free School Correspondence October 1964 (Box-folder 3:4)
    - Free School Correspondence November 1964 (Box-folder 3:5)
    - Free School Correspondence December 1964 (Box-folder 3:6)
    - Free School Correspondence January 1965 (Box-folder 3:7)
    - Free School Correspondence February 1965 (Box-folder 3:8)
    - Free School Correspondence March 1965 (Box-folder 3:9)
    - Free School Correspondence April 1965 (Box-folder 3:10)
    - Free School Correspondence May 1965 (Box-folder 3:11)
    - Free School Correspondence June 1965 (Box-folder 3:12)
    - Free School Correspondence August-December 1965 (Box-folder 3:13)
    - Free School Correspondence Sept 1966 (Box-folder 3:14)
    - Free School Correspondence No Date (Box-folder 3:15)
- Office of the Treasurer/Secretary
  The Treasurer was a member of the board of trustees. And in that position was responsible for: The Budget, Expenditures, Payroll Development, and all donated and loaned equipment.
  - Ribble-Board of Trustees 1963-1964 (Box-folder 4:1)
  - Governor Darden 1963 (Box-folder 4:2)
  - Governor Darden 1964 (Box-folder 4:3)
  - Progress Report 1963 (Box-folder 4:4)
  - Progress Report (draft) 1/1/1964 (Box-folder 4:5)
  - Progress Report 1/8/1964 (Box-folder 4:6)
  - Memo's to Trustees Oct-Nov 1963 (Box-folder 4:7)
  - Memo's to Trustees December 1963 (Box-folder 4:8)
  - Trustees January-April 1964 (Box-folder 4:9)
  - Memo's April 1964 (Box-folder 4:10)
  - Memo's No Date (Box-folder 4:11)
  - Attorney Generals Visit, Arraignments May 1964 (Box-folder 4:12)
  - Prince Edward Free School Association 1963 (Box-folder 4a:1)
  - Prince Edward Free School Association Payroll 1964 (Box-folder 4a:2)
  - Prince Edward School Association Teachers No Date (Box-folder 4a:3)
  - Prince Edward Free School Association Calender Jan-April 1963 (Box-folder 4a:4)
  - Legal Documents, Deeds and Leases 1963 (Box-folder 4a:5)
  - Amendment to Lease (Box-folder 4a:5a)
  - Budget Expenditures 1964 (Box-folder 4a:6)
  - Donated and Loaned 1964 (Box-folder 4a:7)
  - Prince Edward Free School Association List of Contributions 1963 (Box-folder 4a:8)
  - Prince Edward Free School Association Insurance Correspondence 1963-1964 (Box-folder 4a:9)
  - Budget and Expenditures 1963 (Box-folder 4a:10)
  - Proposal for support 1963 (Box-folder 4a:11)
  - Internal Revenue Service (Artificial) 1963 (Box-folder 4a:12)
  - Prince Edward Free School Association National Bank and Trust Company No Date (Box-folder 4a:13)
  - List of Contributors No Date (Box-folder 4a:14)
  - Prince Edward Free School Association Payroll Account 1963 (Box-folder 4a:15)
  - Prince Edward Free School Association Bonds 1964 (Box-folder 4a:16)
  - Library Report 1963 (Box-folder 4a:17)
  - Prince Edward Free School Association Insurance 1964 (Box-folder 4a:18)
  - Prince Edward Free School Association Riggs National Bank 1964 (Box-folder 4a:19)
  - Prince Edward Free School Association 1964 (Box-folder 4a:20)
  - Prince Edward Free School Association Accounting 1964 (Box-folder 4a:21)
  - Working Papers Financial 1963-1964 (Box-folder 4a:22)
  - Memorandum Tax Exempt Status n. d. (Box-folder 4a:23)
  - Prince Edward Free School Association Deed of Lease 1963 (Box-folder 4a:24)
  - Contracts 1964 (Box-folder 4a:25)
  - Prince Edward Free School Bylaws n.d. (Folder 4a:26)
  - Mussleman, Robert 1963-1964 (Box-folder 4a:27)
  - Payroll Working Papers n.d. (Box-folder 5:1)
  - Invoices - Mussleman n.d. (Box-folder 5:2)
  - Invoices - Mussleman n.d. (Box-folder 5:3)
  - Account Analysis n.d. (Box-folder 5:4)
  - Account Analysis n.d. (Box-folder 5:4a)
  - Inventory R. R. Moton High 9-20-63 (Box-folder 5:5)
  - Bus Reports n.d. (Box-folder 5:6)
  - Cafeteria Working Papers n.d. (Box-folder 5:7)
  - Budget Working Papers n.d. (Box-folder 5:8)
  - Inventory n.d. (Box-folder n.d.)
  - Inventory n.d. (Box-folder 5:10)
  - Inventory Worsham August 1964 (Box-folder 6:1)
  - Inventory Moton August 1964 (Box-folder 6:2)
  - Inventory Moton 1964 (Box-folder 6:3)
  - Payroll Information 1963-1964 (Box-folder 6:4)
  - Payroll Information 1964 (Box-folder 6:5)
  - Payroll Information February 1964 (Box-folder 6:6)
  - Estimated Budget 1963-1964 (Box-folder 6:7)
  - Inventory Worsham (Box-folder 6:8)
  - Working Papers (Box-folder 6:9)
  - Trial Balances (Box-folder 6:10)
  - Inventory Branch (Box-folder 6:11)
  - Inventory Branch (Box-folder 6:12)
  - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 6:13)
  - Addresses Employees N.D. (Box-folder 7:1)
  - Adjustment Invoices & Correspondence N.D. (Box-folder 7:2)
  - Applicants N.D. (Box-folder 7:3)
  - Applicants Summer Sessions N.D. (Box-folder 7:4)
  - Athletic Games N.D. (Box-folder 7:5)
  - Auto and Pick up Reports N.D. (Box-folder 7:6)
  - Field Trips Nov 1963-April 1964 (Box-folder 7:7)
  - Field Trips May 1964-July 1964 (Box-folder 7:8)
  - General Correspondence Jan 1964 (Box-folder 7:9)
  - Insurance 1963, 1964 (Box-folder 7:10)
  - Insurance 1963 (Box-folder 7:11)
  - Insurance 1964 (Box-folder 7:12)
  - Insurance Coverage 1964 (Box-folder 7:13)
  - Correspondence Sept 1963 (Box-folder 7:14)
  - Correspondence Oct-Nov 1963 (Box-folder 7:15)
  - Story of the Free School April 1964 (Box-folder 7:16)
  - The Virginia Retirement System 1964 (Box-folder 7:17)
- Office of the Business Manager
  The Business Manager was responsible for the day-to-day operation of the free school. Included in this series are several boxes of cancelled checks.
  - Bids Sept-Dec 1963 (Box-folder 8:1)
  - Bills Oct-Nov 1963 (Box-folder 8:2)
  - Bids 1964 (Box-folder 8:3)
  - Budget Forms (Box-folder 8:4)
  - Budget and Expenditures December 31, 1963 (Box-folder 8:5)
  - Budget Expenditures February 29, 1964 (Box-folder 8:6)
  - Budget Expenditures April 30, 1964 (Box-folder 8:7)
  - Budget and Expenditures May 31, 1964 (Box-folder 8:8)
  - Budget and Expenditures May 31, 1964 (Box-folder 8:9)
  - Budget Expenditures July 27, 1964 (Box-folder 8:10)
  - Business Account: Tax Exemption Cont. Feb 1964 (Box-folder 8:11)
  - Bus Drivers n.d. (Box-folder 8:12)
  - Bus Information n.d. (Box-folder 8:13)
  - Certificate of Title n.d. (Box-folder 8:14)
  - Directory 1963-1964 (Box-folder 8:15)
  - Donated Property 1963-1964 (Box-folder 8:16)
  - Donated and Loaned Property 1964 (Box-folder 8:17)
  - Equipment (Box-folder 8:18)
  - Exemption Certificates (Box-folder 8:19)
  - Exemption Certificates (Box-folder 8:20)
  - Gas-Oil Reports (Box-folder 8:21)
  - Diplomas and Invitations 1964 (Box-folder 8:22)
  - Graduating Class 1964 (Box-folder 8:23)
  - Housing (white) (Box-folder 8:24)
  - Industrial Arts (Supplies and Material) Requisition (Box-folder 8:25)
  - Insurance 1963-1965 (Box-folder 9:1)
  - Insurance Policies 1963-1964 (Box-folder 9:2)
  - Insurance Accident Forms 1963 (Box-folder 9:3)
  - Inventory Directions 1963 (Box-folder 9:4)
  - Invoices Paid May-August 1963 (Box-folder 9:5)
  - Invoice Paid September 1963 (Box-folder 9:6)
  - Invoices Paid October 1963 (Box-folder 9:7)
  - Invoices Paid November 1963 (Box-folder 9:8)
  - Invoices Paid Dec 1963 (Box-folder 9:9)
  - Invoices Dec 1963 (Box-folder 9:10)
  - Invoices Paid December 1963 (Box-folder 9:11)
  - Invoices Paid Jan 1964 (Box-folder 10:1)
  - Invoices Paid Jan 1964 (Box-folder 10:2)
  - Invoices Paid Jan 1964 (Box-folder 10:3)
  - Invoices Paid January 1964 (Box-folder 10:4)
  - Invoices Paid January 1964 (Box-folder 10:5)
  - Invoices Paid February 1964 (Box-folder 10:6)
  - Invoices Paid February 1964 (Box-folder 10:7)
  - Invoices Paid February 1964 (Box-folder 10:8)
  - Invoices Paid March 1964 (Box-folder 10:9)
  - Invoices Paid March 1964 (Box-folder 10:10)
  - Invoices Paid March 1964 (Box-folder 11:1)
  - Invoices Paid March 1964 (Box-folder 11:2)
  - Invoices Paid March 1964 (Box-folder 11:3)
  - Invoices Paid April 1964 (Box-folder 11:4)
  - Invoices Paid April 1964 (Box-folder 11:5)
  - Invoices Paid May 1964 (Box-folder 11:6)
  - Invoices Paid May 1964 (Box-folder 11:7)
  - Invoices Paid May 1964 (Box-folder 11:8)
  - Invoices Paid No Date (Box-folder 11:9)
  - PNB Cafeteria April-June 1964 (Box-folder 12:1)
  - PNB Cafeteria July 1964 (Box-folder 12:2)
  - PNB Cafeteria August 1964 (Box-folder 12:3)
  - School Building Supplies April 1964 (Box-folder 12:4)
  - School Building Supplies May 1964 (Box-folder 12:5)
  - School Building Supplies Aug 1964 (Box-folder 12:6)
  - School Building Supplies Sept 1964 (Box-folder 12:7)
  - School Building Supplies July 1964 (Box-folder 12:8)
  - School Building Supplies July 1964 (Box-folder 12:9)
  - School Building Supplies July 1964 (Box-folder 12:10)
  - School Building Supplies August 1964 (Box-folder 12:11)
  - School Building Supplies August 1964 (Box-folder 12:12)
  - School Building Supplies August 1964 (Box-folder 12:13)
  - School Building Supplies Sept 1964 (Box-folder 12:14)
  - School Building Supplies Sept 1964 (Box-folder 12:15)
  - Office Supplies (Box-folder 13:1)
  - Office Supplies (Box-folder 13:2)
  - Personnel & Salaries through Dec 31, 1963 (Box-folder 13:3)
  - Personnel & Salaries through June 22-Aug 6 (Box-folder 13:4)
  - Professional Staff (Box-folder 13:5)
  - Requisitions (Box-folder 13:6)
  - Record of Telephone Calls (Box-folder 13:7)
  - Paid Drivers Reports (Box-folder 13:8)
  - School Bus Enrollment Report (Box-folder 13:9)
  - School Bus Schedule (Box-folder 13:10)
  - Sports Equipment (materials and supplies) (Box-folder 13:11)
  - State & Federal Exemption letter n.d. (Box-folder 13:12)
  - Statement of Account Nov 30, 1963 (Box-folder 13:13)
  - Teachers Rooster 1964 (Box-folder 13:14)
  - Trail Balance Nov 30, 1963 (Box-folder 13:15)
  - Utilities (Box-folder 13:16)
  - Donated & Loaned Property 1964 (Box-folder 13:17)
  - Payroll Books (Box-folder 14:1)
  - Payroll Books (Box-folder 15:1)
  - Payroll Books (Box-folder 16:1)
  - Payroll Books (Box-folder 17:1)
- The Office of the Superintendent
  Dr. Neil Sullivan was selected as the superintendent of the Free School Association because of his experience with a non-graded school system.
  - Administrative Memo's and Correspondence
    Administrative memos and correspondence. Arranged Chronologically
    - Memo's Sullivan Sept-Nov 1963 (Box-folder 18:1)
    - Memo's Sullivan December 1963 (Box-folder 18:2)
    - Memo's Sullivan January 1964 (Box-folder January 1964)